import { v4 as uuidv4 } from "uuid";

const germanDeck = [
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    front: "the apple",
    back: "der Apfel",
    correct: false,
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    front: "the bed",
    back: "das Bett",
    correct: false,
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    front: "the cat",
    back: "die Katze",
    correct: false,
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    front: "the dog",
    back: "der Hund",
    correct: false,
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    front: "the egg",
    back: "das Ei",
    correct: false,
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    front: "the fish",
    back: "der Fisch",
    correct: false,
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    front: "the grandmother",
    back: "die Großmutter",
    correct: false,
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    front: "the house",
    back: "das Haus",
    correct: false,
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    front: "the information",
    back: "die Information",
    correct: false,
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    front: "the jam",
    back: "die Marmelade",
    correct: false,
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    front: "the knife",
    back: "das Messer",
    correct: false,
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    front: "the lion",
    back: "der Löwe",
    correct: false,
  },
];

export default germanDeck;
